breakingtravelnews.com 2017-12-02

# Privacy Policy | Breaking Travel News

**Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy is applicable to any personal information, which is given by You to Us (“User Information”) via the web site located at www.breakingtravelnews.com (“Site”). This Policy is devised to help you feel more confident about the privacy and security of your personal details.

“You” shall mean you, the user of the Site. “We/Us” means Internet Travel News. The “Site” shall have the meaning as defined above. “Users” means the users of the Site collectively and/or individually as the context allows. “User Information” means the personal details, which may be provided by You to Us via the Site as described above.

We process personal data only in strict compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and associated legislation.

**Data Collection**  
When using the Site You may encounter areas such as games, competitions, chat forums, or subscription where You may be asked to enter User Information. Such User Information will only be used for the purposes stated at the collection point and/or in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

By entering Your User Information, You accept that we may retain Your User Information and that it may be held by Us or any third party company which processes it on Our behalf.

We reserve the right to perform statistical analyses of User’s behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in, and use of, the various areas of the Site and, in addition, to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of Users that have been exposed to or who have clicked on their advertising banners. We will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties.

**Disclosure**  
We shall be entitled to sell or otherwise make available Your User Information in order to send You information about Us and Our affiliates, associated companies and organisations, for the following purposes including, but not limited to :

  1. promotional and/or marketing material about products, services and offers;
  2. market research or compliance;
  3. transfers to third parties as required; and
  4. any requirements imposed by operational law

We are not responsible for any actions or policies of any third parties who request Your User information and Users should check the applicable privacy policy of such third parties.

**Cookies**  
Like most websites, we use cookies to track site usage and trends and to improve the quality and customise your experience of the Breaking Travel News website. We may also use cookies to provide advertising on the Breaking Travel News website. We may also allow certain business partners to place or recognise cookies on your browser for those purposes.  A cookie is a tiny text file that resides on your computer, mobile phone, or other device, and allows us and/or our business partners to recognise you as a user when you return to a Breaking Travel News website using the same computer and web browser. For more detail on how businesses use cookies on websites, please see [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). You can find an overview of the various types of cookies used by Breaking Travel News and/or our business partners, in the table below.

We use cookies for 4 purposes: 

Cookie Type | Purpose  
---|---  
Essential Operational | These cookies are necessary to allow us to operate the Breaking Travel News Website as you have requested. These cookies, for example, let us recognize what type of subscriber you are and then provide you with the services which you are entitled to.  
Performance | These cookies are used by us or our business partners to analyse how the Breaking Travel News website is used.  The cookies also let us monitor how the Breaking Travel News website is performing. These cookies do not let us identify users and we combine the information which they provide us.  We use this information to maintain, operate and continually improve the Breaking Travel News Website.  
Functional | These cookies let us operate certain functions of the Breaking Travel News website in line with the choices you make.  These cookies mean that when you come back to the Breaking Travel News website we can provide you with our services as you have asked for them to be provided, such as knowing your user name and remembering how you have customised our services.  
Targeting/advertising | These cookies are used by us and our business partners to serve you with advertisements when using the Breaking Travel News website.  Some advertisements may be relevant to you and your interests.  These cookies may also help us and our business partners regulate the advertisement you receive and measure the effectiveness of the advert.  Even if we let our business partners place the cookies for advertising we do not identify you to those business partners.  

**Security**  
Security is very important to Us. Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) encryption technology is used for protection of information in transit for any sensitive transactions such as payments. Additional security procedures are in place to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of Your User information. Your User information will not be kept longer than is necessary for the purposes stated at the collection point or in this Privacy Policy.

**Updates**  
You may notify Us of any updates, amendments and corrections to previously collected User Information by using the Feedback Form link in the Contact Us section of the site. Further, upon Your request, We will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete Your User Information from our database; however, it may be impossible to delete Your entry without some residual information remaining because of backups and records of deletions.

We reserve the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update this Privacy Policy.

**Contact**  
Any queries or comments about this policy should be forwarded to info@breakingtravelnews.com

Any site that you may connect to from here is not covered by this Privacy Policy.
